Okay guys let's think about the blue team so you need to detect a specified process token
sorry access token manipulation attack so it's a bit simple so you need to investigate
one of the even tidy 4656 so you can open a logs security log okay so this is the directory
and you need to open the security log and you need to filter it with the 4656 here before
650 so if you investigating the 4656 so here you can find a handle to an object or
a keyster so we know anyway we are going to take a handle so this is the code we are
going to take a handle so that's why we have a we have the even tidy handle to an object
or a keyster and here you can find the process name it's a token stealer.exe and the
object that has been accessed is a win log1.exe so it access to win log1.exe and the process
which was accessed it's a token stealer so now you can find the access mask of X10, X1000 so let
me do some googler of this
it's a code for X1000.exe access mask.
Okay.
Let me open this.
Let me search with the access rights.
This was not giving a property address it.
Yeah now we got an address it X1000 access rights for process query limited information so
in this code we have used the process query limited information so by this way you can find there
is access token manipulation attack has been happened.
So you can learn more about the process query information access right about this access
so but yeah anyway we have completed the investigation so this is how you can easily find out how
the access token manipulation has been executed okay.
Okay let's swap off and we will see you in another video thank you.